<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Social Justice Projects on Created by Sam Killermann</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/tags/social-justice/</link><description>Recent content in Social Justice Projects on Created by Sam Killermann</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.samuelkillermann.com/tags/social-justice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Social Justice, Minus Dogma</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/social-justice-minus-dogma/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/social-justice-minus-dogma/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;If you’re willing to challenge your personal comfort, prioritize bravery over ideological safety, be humble with your learning &amp;amp; generous with your teaching, and push dogma, performance, &amp;amp; posturing to the side in favor of outcomes, action, &amp;amp; authenticity, this is the space you’ve been looking for. We’re thrilled to meet you.&amp;rdquo;
Social Justice, Minus Dogma is a continuation of the work I've been doing for the past few years confronting the social justice dogma.</description></item><item><title>Defining LGBTQ+</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/defining-lgbtq/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/defining-lgbtq/</guid><description>Defining LGBTQ+, A Guide to Gender &amp;amp; Sexuality Terminology is a printer-friendly (8.5&amp;rdquo; x 11&amp;rdquo; format), short e-book (just 37 pages), that is better thought of as an elaborately annotated glossary than a book-book.
It originated from the glossary of A Guide to Gender and my post Comprehensive List of LGBTQ+ Vocabulary Definitions, which evolved into a collaboration with Meg Bolger as the Core Vocabulary for our Foundational Safe Zone Curriculum.</description></item><item><title>Safe Zone Train-the-Trainer Retreat Guide</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/train-the-trainer-retreat-guide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/train-the-trainer-retreat-guide/</guid><description>As part of our ongoing Train-the-Trainer Toolkit, Meg &amp;amp; I wrote and published a comprehensive retreat guide for Safe Zone Train-the-Trainers.
It includes (from the blog post announcement):
All the individual activities we’d recommend for a TTT, from the LGBTQ+ content knowledge to the facilitator skills Advice on logistics, participant selection, supplies, prep, etc. A retreat schedule with detailed walkthroughs for every step And a whole lot more. Like with our Foundational Curriculum, we offer this to you as editable Google Docs for your customizing convenience.</description></item><item><title>The Heretic Podcast</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/heretic/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/heretic/</guid><description>With guest activists, authors, and artists who have who have been pushed to the fringes by the movement, spent their lives fighting for social justice, or fighting against it, Heretic is a light conversation about the darkness in society.
It's also the scariest thing I've ever done.
I started writing about The Social Justice Dogma on It's Pronounced Metrosexual in December of 2017.
Visual Design + Identity The branding of Heretic is sunny day at the beach meets Da Vinci Code.</description></item><item><title>The Safe Zone Project 2.0</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project-2/</guid><description>The Safe Zone Project 2.0 is what Meg &amp;amp; I have been saying to refer to the revamp of the online resource, so that's what I'll call it here.
Highlights of Version 2.0:
Online courses, with a seamlessly integrated learning management system A clearinghouse of resources for launching your own Safe Zone program (called the Train-the-Trainer Toolkit) Improved accessibility, site structure, usability, and site speed A new record for curriculum downloads in a month: 1,432 (our old record was 690) Backstory Meg and I initially created The Safe Zone Project in 2013 to serve as a free online resource for folks doing LGBTQ awareness and ally trainings (AKA &amp;ldquo;safe zone trainings&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>Every Shirt is Political</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/every-shirt-is-political/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/every-shirt-is-political/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Every shirt is political. It’s not just about what a shirt says on the front; it’s about what you’re saying when you buy it or wear it.
If you buy a shirt that was manufactured with unethical labor, you’re making a statement in favor of abuse. The same goes for the corporation who you buy it from, or the materials it’s made with.&amp;rdquo; (from the About Page)</description></item><item><title>Columns &amp; Shadows Healthy Relationship Model</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/rest-columns-shadows-healthy-relationship-model/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/rest-columns-shadows-healthy-relationship-model/</guid><description>I co-created the Columns &amp;amp; Shadows model with friend / sex educator / curriculum writer extraordinaire Karen Rayne. We put our heads together to help sex educators answer a question a lot of students struggle with: what makes a relationship healthy or unhealthy?
Here's a quote from article I wrote to introduce the Columns &amp;amp; Shadows Model:
&amp;ldquo;It’s hard to define what a healthy relationship looks like because we all navigate relationships differently.</description></item><item><title>I Heart Singular They</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/i-heart-singular-they/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/i-heart-singular-they/</guid><description>This adorable, shareable, and oh-so-subtly-activist love poem was inspired by Everyone in the 90s’ experience in high school.
“Writing with non-gender-neutral pronouns is a serious pain. Some prefer the Frankenword “s/he,” while others rack their brain. Some stick with a particular pronoun for one paragraph or chapter, then swap out the one they’re using; thers alternate “he” and “she” by sentence, or use a plural adapter, but that all sounds confusing.</description></item><item><title>TEDxTalk: Do the W.O.R.K.</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/ted-x-talk-do-the-work/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/ted-x-talk-do-the-work/</guid><description>My third (and final) TEDxTalk, where I present a sort of unified theory of social justice, explaining what it means to &amp;ldquo;do the work,&amp;rdquo; and how we can do it.
I performed this talk at TEDxYouth in San Diego for the theme &amp;ldquo;We Can't Wait.&amp;rdquo; I combined theories from some of my favorite thinkers to create a road map for aspiring social justice advocates.
Unfortunately, due to technical difficulties, video from the event didn't make it to TED's site or YouTube.</description></item><item><title>Socially Just Cards</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/socially-just-cards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/socially-just-cards/</guid><description>An experiment in gift economy and social justice, SJC is where I serve as Head Elf.
The cards are all doodled and written by me, but that's not the important part.
What's exciting about this project was the bar I set for myself: can I create a business that sells a physical thing that is 100% socially/environmentally/globally just. That is, that doesn't create harm or compromise in any way.
SJC is what was born.</description></item><item><title>All Gender Restroom Sign</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/all-gender-restroom-sign/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/all-gender-restroom-sign/</guid><description>This is the project that led to The New York Times publishing &amp;ldquo;[Killermann is] perfectly O.K. with being known as the toilet sign guy.&amp;rdquo;
Damn right I am, New York Times! Nothing would make me happier.
You can read all about how this sign came to be on It's Pronounced Metrosexual, and I won't repeat myself here. What I'll say instead are a few things that I don't think I've written:</description></item><item><title>A Guide to Gender</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/guide-to-gender/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/guide-to-gender/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;A book about gender with no mention of the word &amp;lsquo;hegemony,&amp;rsquo; but plenty of references to Star Wars, The Matrix, Lord of the Rings, and Star Trek&amp;ndash; with less of a focus on overwhelming scholarship and more of a focus on enjoyable learning.&amp;rdquo; (excerpt from the book's (first edition) description)
I wrote this book because a bunch of people asked me to. It was a synthesis of the ideas (1) I had been blogging about; (2) I'd been speaking about; and (3) that helped me better understand my gender, when I first set down the path of understanding.</description></item><item><title>The Safe Zone Project</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project/</guid><description>Meg and I created The Safe Zone Project in 2013 to serve as a free online resource for folks doing LGBTQ awareness and ally trainings (AKA &amp;ldquo;safe zone trainings&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>You Soup</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/you-soup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/you-soup/</guid><description>You have been told all your life that you’re unique, you’re special, like a snowflake. Nobody is like you, you’re one in 7 billion (or one in 108 billion, an estimated total number of humans ever, if you want to get technical), and nobody can take that away from you.
Yet at the same time you’ve been told that you can guess that someone else will be like everyone else in a particular group based on their membership in that group (e.</description></item><item><title>The Genderbread Person</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/genderbread-person/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/genderbread-person/</guid><description>I published my first version of the Genderbread Person, an adorable, digestible model for understanding the complexity of gender, to accompany an essay in 2011 (and made a more printer-friendly version early in 2012).
I went on to create several versions of this model, improving and tweaking it based on feedback, and it's been adapted and remixed by countless other educators and organizations over the years.
This was my spin on an idea that I was taught on back in college (in the early 2000s), which goes back in different forms for many decades.</description></item><item><title>It's Pronounced Metrosexual</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/its-pronounced-metrosexual/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/its-pronounced-metrosexual/</guid><description>I wrote the show that became &amp;ldquo;It's Pronounced Metrosexual&amp;rdquo; while I was in grad school.
It was my &amp;ldquo;Plan B&amp;rdquo; for if I don't find a job in higher education. We were still in a recession, and jobs were tough to come by.
The online resource aspect of IPM, by about 100-fold the most popular byproduct of the site, was the result of a suggestion by my partner at the time.</description></item></channel></rss>