<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Facilitation on Created by Sam Killermann</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/tags/facilitation/</link><description>Recent content in Facilitation on Created by Sam Killermann</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.samuelkillermann.com/tags/facilitation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Facilitating XYZ</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/facilitating-xyz/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/facilitating-xyz/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;When many of us start facilitating, we find ourselves learning a new skill without a lot of guidance or direction. We are passionate about the information and content that we are communicating, but we’re often less versed in tips and techniques regarding how to communicate that information.
This project is a free online resource that is to ensure that none of us have to navigate this world of facilitation without guidance, direction, or support.</description></item><item><title>Unlocking the Magic of Facilitation</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/unlocking-the-magic-of-facilitation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/unlocking-the-magic-of-facilitation/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Have you ever been in a training and marveled at how quickly the time flew by?
Genuinely enjoyed a meeting you were expecting to dread? Learned something powerful about a topic you thought wouldn't engage you? Experienced an intimate, vulnerable, transformative moment with a group of total strangers? Then you've witnessed the magic of facilitation.&amp;rdquo; (excerpt from the book description)
I wrote Unlocking the Magic of Facilitation with Meg Bolger, after spending a few years doing train-the-trainers with her through The Safe Zone Project.</description></item></channel></rss>