<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gift Experiment on Created by Sam Killermann</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/tags/gift-experiment/</link><description>Recent content in Gift Experiment on Created by Sam Killermann</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.samuelkillermann.com/tags/gift-experiment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Social Justice, Minus Dogma</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/social-justice-minus-dogma/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/social-justice-minus-dogma/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;If you’re willing to challenge your personal comfort, prioritize bravery over ideological safety, be humble with your learning &amp;amp; generous with your teaching, and push dogma, performance, &amp;amp; posturing to the side in favor of outcomes, action, &amp;amp; authenticity, this is the space you’ve been looking for. We’re thrilled to meet you.&amp;rdquo;
Social Justice, Minus Dogma is a continuation of the work I've been doing for the past few years confronting the social justice dogma.</description></item><item><title>Be My Boss(es)</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/be-my-bosses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/be-my-bosses/</guid><description>Be My Boss(es) is a splash page for my Patreon profile, explaining how I am doing Patreon, and patronage, for anyone who wants to employ me.
I built it with Hugo and it's being served up with Netlify &amp;ndash; just like this site you're reading this on.</description></item><item><title>Every Shirt is Political</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/every-shirt-is-political/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/every-shirt-is-political/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Every shirt is political. It’s not just about what a shirt says on the front; it’s about what you’re saying when you buy it or wear it.
If you buy a shirt that was manufactured with unethical labor, you’re making a statement in favor of abuse. The same goes for the corporation who you buy it from, or the materials it’s made with.&amp;rdquo; (from the About Page)</description></item><item><title>Socially Just Cards</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/socially-just-cards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/socially-just-cards/</guid><description>An experiment in gift economy and social justice, SJC is where I serve as Head Elf.
The cards are all doodled and written by me, but that's not the important part.
What's exciting about this project was the bar I set for myself: can I create a business that sells a physical thing that is 100% socially/environmentally/globally just. That is, that doesn't create harm or compromise in any way.
SJC is what was born.</description></item></channel></rss>