<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Copywriter on Created by Sam Killermann</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/skills/copywriter/</link><description>Recent content in Copywriter on Created by Sam Killermann</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.samuelkillermann.com/skills/copywriter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Every Shirt is Political</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/every-shirt-is-political/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/every-shirt-is-political/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Every shirt is political. It’s not just about what a shirt says on the front; it’s about what you’re saying when you buy it or wear it.
If you buy a shirt that was manufactured with unethical labor, you’re making a statement in favor of abuse. The same goes for the corporation who you buy it from, or the materials it’s made with.&amp;rdquo; (from the About Page)</description></item><item><title>Columns &amp; Shadows Healthy Relationship Model</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/rest-columns-shadows-healthy-relationship-model/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/rest-columns-shadows-healthy-relationship-model/</guid><description>I co-created the Columns &amp;amp; Shadows model with friend / sex educator / curriculum writer extraordinaire Karen Rayne. We put our heads together to help sex educators answer a question a lot of students struggle with: what makes a relationship healthy or unhealthy?
Here's a quote from article I wrote to introduce the Columns &amp;amp; Shadows Model:
&amp;ldquo;It’s hard to define what a healthy relationship looks like because we all navigate relationships differently.</description></item><item><title>Socially Just Cards</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/socially-just-cards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/socially-just-cards/</guid><description>An experiment in gift economy and social justice, SJC is where I serve as Head Elf.
The cards are all doodled and written by me, but that's not the important part.
What's exciting about this project was the bar I set for myself: can I create a business that sells a physical thing that is 100% socially/environmentally/globally just. That is, that doesn't create harm or compromise in any way.
SJC is what was born.</description></item></channel></rss>