<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>All Work on Sam Killermann&#39;s Curriculum Vitae</title>
    <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in All Work on Sam Killermann&#39;s Curriculum Vitae</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://samuelkillermann.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/links/</guid>
      <description>Click and behold: hypertext transfer protocol at its finest.
First, a fancy little list of the things I&amp;rsquo;m guessing most of you are looking for (and maybe some optimistic nudging toward things I want you to be looking for):
Blog Podcast Patreon Gender Book Facilitation Book The hues Store
Professional Links (for potential clients, bookings, etc.) Are you looking to&amp;hellip;
 Invite me to speak at your event: http://samtalkto.us Book me to perform a campus program: http://itspronouncedmetrosexual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Site: Samuel Killermann Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/samuel-killermann-curriculum-vitae/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/samuel-killermann-curriculum-vitae/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the seventh version of samuelkillermann.com. At least &amp;ndash; I think that&amp;rsquo;s right. One thing I&amp;rsquo;m sure of: it&amp;rsquo;s been a linear path of &amp;ldquo;Each one is better than the last.&amp;rdquo;
Sometimes embarrassingly better. If you&amp;rsquo;re curious about what the old versions of this site looked like, by all means step into the Wayback Machine and take a tour. Don&amp;rsquo;t say I didn&amp;rsquo;t warn you.
So let&amp;rsquo;s talk about what I&amp;rsquo;ve got going on here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Sam Killermann</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s be honest: &amp;ldquo;About&amp;rdquo; pages are pretty bleh. For a more fun idea, check out the &amp;ldquo;Now&amp;rdquo; page on this site.
Okay, now that I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten that off my chest &amp;mdash; Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Sam, and I wear a lot of hats. If you&amp;rsquo;ve poked around this site, specifically the work list, you&amp;rsquo;ve likely already figured that out.
I&amp;rsquo;m not really sure what you want to know about me, so I&amp;rsquo;ll do my best to answer the most common questions I get asked from crowd members and readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Restructuring Everything</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/now/may-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/now/may-2018/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m writing from a coffee shop in Austin, TX where I just spent two hours trying to get this site to deploy on Netlify. Annnnd success?
Success.
This site is part of a huge life restructuring I&amp;rsquo;m currently undertaking. I wrote about it on my blog, but here&amp;rsquo;s the highlighted version:
 My primary org (hues) dissolved in its original vision at the beginning of this year I&amp;rsquo;m no longer with a speaking/talent agency (for the first time in half a decade) And as a result, I&amp;rsquo;ve started to rethink everything I do, mostly in the &amp;ldquo;Can I, and/or do I want to, keep doing this thing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sam Killermann Biography</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/bio/</guid>
      <description>Sam Killermann is a comedian, author, and award-winning activist. Sam travels the world performing comedy shows and giving talks on themes of social justice, gender, and sexuality.
Killermann&amp;rsquo;s work (that he uncopyrighted in 2013) has been downloaded by hundreds of millions of people around the world who utilize it to bolster their educational efforts toward global equity. His versions of the Genderbread Person, a model for understanding and teaching gender and sexual diversity, have been translated into over a dozen languages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Magic of Facilitation</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/unlocking-the-magic-of-facilitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/unlocking-the-magic-of-facilitation/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Have you ever been in a training and marveled at how quickly the time flew by?
Genuinely enjoyed a meeting you were expecting to dread? Learned something powerful about a topic you thought wouldn&amp;rsquo;t engage you? Experienced an intimate, vulnerable, transformative moment with a group of total strangers? Then you&amp;rsquo;ve witnessed the magic of facilitation.&amp;rdquo; (excerpt from the book description)
I wrote Unlocking the Magic of Facilitation with Meg Bolger, after spending a few years doing train-the-trainers with her through The Safe Zone Project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Guide to Gender</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/guide-to-gender/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/guide-to-gender/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A book about gender with no mention of the word &amp;lsquo;hegemony,&amp;rsquo; but plenty of references to Star Wars, The Matrix, Lord of the Rings, and Star Trek&amp;ndash; with less of a focus on overwhelming scholarship and more of a focus on enjoyable learning.&amp;rdquo; (excerpt from the book&amp;rsquo;s (first edition) description)
I wrote this book because a lot of people asked me to. It was a synthesis of a lot of the ideas (1) I had been blogging about; (2) I&amp;rsquo;d been speaking about; and (3) that helped me better understand my gender, when I first set down the path of understanding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Safe Zone Project</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project/</guid>
      <description>Meg and I created The Safe Zone Project in 2013 to serve as a free online resource for folks doing LGBTQ awareness and ally trainings (AKA &amp;ldquo;safe zone trainings&amp;rdquo;).
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Pronounced Metrosexual</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/its-pronounced-metrosexual/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/its-pronounced-metrosexual/</guid>
      <description>I wrote the show that became &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s Pronounced Metrosexual&amp;rdquo; while I was in grad school.
It was my &amp;ldquo;Plan B&amp;rdquo; for if I don&amp;rsquo;t find a job in higher education. We were still in a recession, and jobs were tough to come by.
The online resource aspect of IPM, by about 100-fold the most popular byproduct of the site, was the result of a suggestion by my partner at the time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>