<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>What am I up to right meow? on Created by Sam Killermann</title>
    <link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/now/</link>
    <description>Recent content in What am I up to right meow? on Created by Sam Killermann</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.samuelkillermann.com/now/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Justice, Minus Dogma &#43; Facilitator Cards</title>
      <link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/now/2019-april/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/now/2019-april/</guid>
      <description>I am in the process of creating two big new projects. Both are well underway, with lots of things you can check out right now.
One is a Social Justice, Minus Dogma Online Course &amp;amp; Community, which lives at www.sjmd.space.
This was the result of asking people on IPM if it was something they&amp;rsquo;d want, and having (now) thousands of people reply &amp;ldquo;Yes!&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;m creating the project in the spirit of a MOOC, but with a lot of twists and turns in response to the delicate &amp;ndash; and potentially nuclear &amp;ndash; nature of our subject.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting bossed around.</title>
      <link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/now/2019-january/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/now/2019-january/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;In most cases being a good boss means hiring talented people and then getting out of their way.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;mdash; Tina Fey
 For 2019, I&amp;rsquo;m trying something new: I&amp;rsquo;m searching for bosses.
2018 was a year of intense reflection, and reorganization.
I took baby steps to try to fund my online work directly (instead of how I&amp;rsquo;d been doing it before, by speaking &amp;amp; performing &amp;ndash; from &amp;ldquo;behind the curtain&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heresy.</title>
      <link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/now/2018-october/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/now/2018-october/</guid>
      <description>“Progress is born of doubt and inquiry. The Church never doubts, never inquires. To doubt is heresy, to inquire is to admit that you do not know—the Church does neither.”
&amp;mdash; Robert G. Ingersoll
 Now, in bullets:  I&amp;rsquo;m working on my podcast, Heretic: Social Justice, Minus Dogma (Wanna help? Or suggest a guest? Click here.) Publishing regular content about gender, sexuality, and social justice at It&amp;rsquo;s Pronounced Metrosexual No longer accepting requests for IPM Shows or campus programs Creating merch for The hues Store Contributing my first official plugin to the Wordpress Directory (free, open source)  Now, in miscellanea:  Reading (devouring) Climate: A New Story by Charles Eisenstein Listening to Nightmare Before Christmas on repeat Relishing the spooky season, sweater season, scarf season, my favorite season, in Austin, TX  Now, in prose: My life, right now, is one full of doubt and inquiry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SZP Website Re-making, Puppy Loving, Class Taking, Podcast Recording, &amp; Article Writing</title>
      <link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/now/june-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/now/june-2018/</guid>
      <description>My now is a lot of new.
The first new &amp;ndash; and this is 100% the most important thing I&amp;rsquo;m working on &amp;ndash; is learning all things puppy. Training? Feeding? Pooping? Scooping? Yes.
As any other expecting parent in 2018, I&amp;rsquo;ve turned to the internet for help.
Good news: lots of people have great advice for me and my pup.
Great news: I&amp;rsquo;m still not an anti-vaxxer.
The new pup is a Morkie, and he&amp;rsquo;ll be making a debut on my Insta any time now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Restructuring Everything</title>
      <link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/now/may-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/now/may-2018/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m writing from a coffee shop in Austin, TX where I just spent two hours trying to get this site to deploy on Netlify. Annnnd success?
Success.
This site is part of a huge life restructuring I&amp;rsquo;m currently undertaking. I wrote about it on my blog, but here&amp;rsquo;s the highlighted version:
 My primary org (hues) dissolved in its original vision at the beginning of this year I&amp;rsquo;m no longer with a speaking/talent agency (for the first time in half a decade) And as a result, I&amp;rsquo;ve started to rethink everything I do, mostly in the &amp;ldquo;Can I, and/or do I want to, keep doing this thing?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>