<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Author on Created by Sam Killermann</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/skills/author/</link><description>Recent content in Author on Created by Sam Killermann</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.samuelkillermann.com/skills/author/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Defining LGBTQ+</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/defining-lgbtq/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/defining-lgbtq/</guid><description>Defining LGBTQ+, A Guide to Gender &amp;amp; Sexuality Terminology is a printer-friendly (8.5&amp;rdquo; x 11&amp;rdquo; format), short e-book (just 37 pages), that is better thought of as an elaborately annotated glossary than a book-book.
It originated from the glossary of A Guide to Gender and my post Comprehensive List of LGBTQ+ Vocabulary Definitions, which evolved into a collaboration with Meg Bolger as the Core Vocabulary for our Foundational Safe Zone Curriculum.</description></item><item><title>I Heart Singular They</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/i-heart-singular-they/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/i-heart-singular-they/</guid><description>This adorable, shareable, and oh-so-subtly-activist love poem was inspired by Everyone in the 90s’ experience in high school.
“Writing with non-gender-neutral pronouns is a serious pain. Some prefer the Frankenword “s/he,” while others rack their brain. Some stick with a particular pronoun for one paragraph or chapter, then swap out the one they’re using; thers alternate “he” and “she” by sentence, or use a plural adapter, but that all sounds confusing.</description></item><item><title>Unlocking the Magic of Facilitation</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/unlocking-the-magic-of-facilitation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/unlocking-the-magic-of-facilitation/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Have you ever been in a training and marveled at how quickly the time flew by?
Genuinely enjoyed a meeting you were expecting to dread? Learned something powerful about a topic you thought wouldn't engage you? Experienced an intimate, vulnerable, transformative moment with a group of total strangers? Then you've witnessed the magic of facilitation.&amp;rdquo; (excerpt from the book description)
I wrote Unlocking the Magic of Facilitation with Meg Bolger, after spending a few years doing train-the-trainers with her through The Safe Zone Project.</description></item><item><title>A Guide to Gender</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/guide-to-gender/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/guide-to-gender/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;A book about gender with no mention of the word &amp;lsquo;hegemony,&amp;rsquo; but plenty of references to Star Wars, The Matrix, Lord of the Rings, and Star Trek&amp;ndash; with less of a focus on overwhelming scholarship and more of a focus on enjoyable learning.&amp;rdquo; (excerpt from the book's (first edition) description)
I wrote this book because a bunch of people asked me to. It was a synthesis of the ideas (1) I had been blogging about; (2) I'd been speaking about; and (3) that helped me better understand my gender, when I first set down the path of understanding.</description></item></channel></rss>