<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Public Thinker on Sam Killermann&#39;s Curriculum Vitae</title>
    <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/skills/public-thinker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Public Thinker on Sam Killermann&#39;s Curriculum Vitae</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://samuelkillermann.com/skills/public-thinker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Magic of Facilitation</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/unlocking-the-magic-of-facilitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/unlocking-the-magic-of-facilitation/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Have you ever been in a training and marveled at how quickly the time flew by?
Genuinely enjoyed a meeting you were expecting to dread? Learned something powerful about a topic you thought wouldn&amp;rsquo;t engage you? Experienced an intimate, vulnerable, transformative moment with a group of total strangers? Then you&amp;rsquo;ve witnessed the magic of facilitation.&amp;rdquo; (excerpt from the book description)
I wrote Unlocking the Magic of Facilitation with Meg Bolger, after spending a few years doing train-the-trainers with her through The Safe Zone Project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Guide to Gender</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/guide-to-gender/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/guide-to-gender/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A book about gender with no mention of the word &amp;lsquo;hegemony,&amp;rsquo; but plenty of references to Star Wars, The Matrix, Lord of the Rings, and Star Trek&amp;ndash; with less of a focus on overwhelming scholarship and more of a focus on enjoyable learning.&amp;rdquo; (excerpt from the book&amp;rsquo;s (first edition) description)
I wrote this book because a bunch of people asked me to. It was a synthesis of the ideas (1) I had been blogging about; (2) I&amp;rsquo;d been speaking about; and (3) that helped me better understand my gender, when I first set down the path of understanding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Pronounced Metrosexual</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/its-pronounced-metrosexual/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/its-pronounced-metrosexual/</guid>
      <description>I wrote the show that became &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s Pronounced Metrosexual&amp;rdquo; while I was in grad school.
It was my &amp;ldquo;Plan B&amp;rdquo; for if I don&amp;rsquo;t find a job in higher education. We were still in a recession, and jobs were tough to come by.
The online resource aspect of IPM, by about 100-fold the most popular byproduct of the site, was the result of a suggestion by my partner at the time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>