<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Online Course on Created by Sam Killermann</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/tags/online-course/</link><description>Recent content in Online Course on Created by Sam Killermann</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.samuelkillermann.com/tags/online-course/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Social Justice, Minus Dogma</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/social-justice-minus-dogma/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/social-justice-minus-dogma/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;If you’re willing to challenge your personal comfort, prioritize bravery over ideological safety, be humble with your learning &amp;amp; generous with your teaching, and push dogma, performance, &amp;amp; posturing to the side in favor of outcomes, action, &amp;amp; authenticity, this is the space you’ve been looking for. We’re thrilled to meet you.&amp;rdquo;
Social Justice, Minus Dogma is a continuation of the work I've been doing for the past few years confronting the social justice dogma.</description></item><item><title>The Safe Zone Project 2.0</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project-2/</guid><description>The Safe Zone Project 2.0 is what Meg &amp;amp; I have been saying to refer to the revamp of the online resource, so that's what I'll call it here.
Highlights of Version 2.0:
Online courses, with a seamlessly integrated learning management system A clearinghouse of resources for launching your own Safe Zone program (called the Train-the-Trainer Toolkit) Improved accessibility, site structure, usability, and site speed A new record for curriculum downloads in a month: 1,432 (our old record was 690) Backstory Meg and I initially created The Safe Zone Project in 2013 to serve as a free online resource for folks doing LGBTQ awareness and ally trainings (AKA &amp;ldquo;safe zone trainings&amp;rdquo;).</description></item></channel></rss>