<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Curriculum Writer on Created by Sam Killermann</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/skills/curriculum-writer/</link><description>Recent content in Curriculum Writer on Created by Sam Killermann</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.samuelkillermann.com/skills/curriculum-writer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Safe Zone Train-the-Trainer Retreat Guide</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/train-the-trainer-retreat-guide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/train-the-trainer-retreat-guide/</guid><description>As part of our ongoing Train-the-Trainer Toolkit, Meg &amp;amp; I wrote and published a comprehensive retreat guide for Safe Zone Train-the-Trainers.
It includes (from the blog post announcement):
All the individual activities we’d recommend for a TTT, from the LGBTQ+ content knowledge to the facilitator skills Advice on logistics, participant selection, supplies, prep, etc. A retreat schedule with detailed walkthroughs for every step And a whole lot more. Like with our Foundational Curriculum, we offer this to you as editable Google Docs for your customizing convenience.</description></item><item><title>The Safe Zone Project 2.0</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project-2/</guid><description>The Safe Zone Project 2.0 is what Meg &amp;amp; I have been saying to refer to the revamp of the online resource, so that's what I'll call it here.
Highlights of Version 2.0:
Online courses, with a seamlessly integrated learning management system A clearinghouse of resources for launching your own Safe Zone program (called the Train-the-Trainer Toolkit) Improved accessibility, site structure, usability, and site speed A new record for curriculum downloads in a month: 1,432 (our old record was 690) Backstory Meg and I initially created The Safe Zone Project in 2013 to serve as a free online resource for folks doing LGBTQ awareness and ally trainings (AKA &amp;ldquo;safe zone trainings&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>The Safe Zone Project</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project/</guid><description>Meg and I created The Safe Zone Project in 2013 to serve as a free online resource for folks doing LGBTQ awareness and ally trainings (AKA &amp;ldquo;safe zone trainings&amp;rdquo;).</description></item></channel></rss>