<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Facilitator on Created by Sam Killermann</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/skills/facilitator/</link><description>Recent content in Facilitator on Created by Sam Killermann</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.samuelkillermann.com/skills/facilitator/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Social Justice, Minus Dogma</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/social-justice-minus-dogma/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/social-justice-minus-dogma/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;If you’re willing to challenge your personal comfort, prioritize bravery over ideological safety, be humble with your learning &amp;amp; generous with your teaching, and push dogma, performance, &amp;amp; posturing to the side in favor of outcomes, action, &amp;amp; authenticity, this is the space you’ve been looking for. We’re thrilled to meet you.&amp;rdquo;
Social Justice, Minus Dogma is a continuation of the work I've been doing for the past few years confronting the social justice dogma.</description></item><item><title>Safe Zone Train-the-Trainer Retreat Guide</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/train-the-trainer-retreat-guide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/train-the-trainer-retreat-guide/</guid><description>As part of our ongoing Train-the-Trainer Toolkit, Meg &amp;amp; I wrote and published a comprehensive retreat guide for Safe Zone Train-the-Trainers.
It includes (from the blog post announcement):
All the individual activities we’d recommend for a TTT, from the LGBTQ+ content knowledge to the facilitator skills Advice on logistics, participant selection, supplies, prep, etc. A retreat schedule with detailed walkthroughs for every step And a whole lot more. Like with our Foundational Curriculum, we offer this to you as editable Google Docs for your customizing convenience.</description></item><item><title>The Heretic Podcast</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/heretic/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/heretic/</guid><description>With guest activists, authors, and artists who have who have been pushed to the fringes by the movement, spent their lives fighting for social justice, or fighting against it, Heretic is a light conversation about the darkness in society.
It's also the scariest thing I've ever done.
I started writing about The Social Justice Dogma on It's Pronounced Metrosexual in December of 2017.
Visual Design + Identity The branding of Heretic is sunny day at the beach meets Da Vinci Code.</description></item><item><title>The Safe Zone Project 2.0</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project-2/</guid><description>The Safe Zone Project 2.0 is what Meg &amp;amp; I have been saying to refer to the revamp of the online resource, so that's what I'll call it here.
Highlights of Version 2.0:
Online courses, with a seamlessly integrated learning management system A clearinghouse of resources for launching your own Safe Zone program (called the Train-the-Trainer Toolkit) Improved accessibility, site structure, usability, and site speed A new record for curriculum downloads in a month: 1,432 (our old record was 690) Backstory Meg and I initially created The Safe Zone Project in 2013 to serve as a free online resource for folks doing LGBTQ awareness and ally trainings (AKA &amp;ldquo;safe zone trainings&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>Facilitating XYZ</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/facilitating-xyz/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/facilitating-xyz/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;When many of us start facilitating, we find ourselves learning a new skill without a lot of guidance or direction. We are passionate about the information and content that we are communicating, but we’re often less versed in tips and techniques regarding how to communicate that information.
This project is a free online resource that is to ensure that none of us have to navigate this world of facilitation without guidance, direction, or support.</description></item><item><title>Unlocking the Magic of Facilitation</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/unlocking-the-magic-of-facilitation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/unlocking-the-magic-of-facilitation/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Have you ever been in a training and marveled at how quickly the time flew by?
Genuinely enjoyed a meeting you were expecting to dread? Learned something powerful about a topic you thought wouldn't engage you? Experienced an intimate, vulnerable, transformative moment with a group of total strangers? Then you've witnessed the magic of facilitation.&amp;rdquo; (excerpt from the book description)
I wrote Unlocking the Magic of Facilitation with Meg Bolger, after spending a few years doing train-the-trainers with her through The Safe Zone Project.</description></item><item><title>The Safe Zone Project</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project/</guid><description>Meg and I created The Safe Zone Project in 2013 to serve as a free online resource for folks doing LGBTQ awareness and ally trainings (AKA &amp;ldquo;safe zone trainings&amp;rdquo;).</description></item></channel></rss>