<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogger on Created by Sam Killermann</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/skills/blogger/</link><description>Recent content in Blogger on Created by Sam Killermann</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.samuelkillermann.com/skills/blogger/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Facilitating XYZ</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/facilitating-xyz/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/facilitating-xyz/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;When many of us start facilitating, we find ourselves learning a new skill without a lot of guidance or direction. We are passionate about the information and content that we are communicating, but we’re often less versed in tips and techniques regarding how to communicate that information.
This project is a free online resource that is to ensure that none of us have to navigate this world of facilitation without guidance, direction, or support.</description></item><item><title>All Gender Restroom Sign</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/all-gender-restroom-sign/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/all-gender-restroom-sign/</guid><description>This is the project that led to The New York Times publishing &amp;ldquo;[Killermann is] perfectly O.K. with being known as the toilet sign guy.&amp;rdquo;
Damn right I am, New York Times! Nothing would make me happier.
You can read all about how this sign came to be on It's Pronounced Metrosexual, and I won't repeat myself here. What I'll say instead are a few things that I don't think I've written:</description></item><item><title>It's Pronounced Metrosexual</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/its-pronounced-metrosexual/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/its-pronounced-metrosexual/</guid><description>I wrote the show that became &amp;ldquo;It's Pronounced Metrosexual&amp;rdquo; while I was in grad school.
It was my &amp;ldquo;Plan B&amp;rdquo; for if I don't find a job in higher education. We were still in a recession, and jobs were tough to come by.
The online resource aspect of IPM, by about 100-fold the most popular byproduct of the site, was the result of a suggestion by my partner at the time.</description></item></channel></rss>