<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sexuality on Created by Sam Killermann</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/tags/sexuality/</link><description>Recent content in Sexuality on Created by Sam Killermann</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.samuelkillermann.com/tags/sexuality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Defining LGBTQ+</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/defining-lgbtq/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/defining-lgbtq/</guid><description>Defining LGBTQ+, A Guide to Gender &amp;amp; Sexuality Terminology is a printer-friendly (8.5&amp;rdquo; x 11&amp;rdquo; format), short e-book (just 37 pages), that is better thought of as an elaborately annotated glossary than a book-book.
It originated from the glossary of A Guide to Gender and my post Comprehensive List of LGBTQ+ Vocabulary Definitions, which evolved into a collaboration with Meg Bolger as the Core Vocabulary for our Foundational Safe Zone Curriculum.</description></item><item><title>Safe Zone Train-the-Trainer Retreat Guide</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/train-the-trainer-retreat-guide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/train-the-trainer-retreat-guide/</guid><description>As part of our ongoing Train-the-Trainer Toolkit, Meg &amp;amp; I wrote and published a comprehensive retreat guide for Safe Zone Train-the-Trainers.
It includes (from the blog post announcement):
All the individual activities we’d recommend for a TTT, from the LGBTQ+ content knowledge to the facilitator skills Advice on logistics, participant selection, supplies, prep, etc. A retreat schedule with detailed walkthroughs for every step And a whole lot more. Like with our Foundational Curriculum, we offer this to you as editable Google Docs for your customizing convenience.</description></item><item><title>The Safe Zone Project 2.0</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project-2/</guid><description>The Safe Zone Project 2.0 is what Meg &amp;amp; I have been saying to refer to the revamp of the online resource, so that's what I'll call it here.
Highlights of Version 2.0:
Online courses, with a seamlessly integrated learning management system A clearinghouse of resources for launching your own Safe Zone program (called the Train-the-Trainer Toolkit) Improved accessibility, site structure, usability, and site speed A new record for curriculum downloads in a month: 1,432 (our old record was 690) Backstory Meg and I initially created The Safe Zone Project in 2013 to serve as a free online resource for folks doing LGBTQ awareness and ally trainings (AKA &amp;ldquo;safe zone trainings&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>Columns &amp; Shadows Healthy Relationship Model</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/rest-columns-shadows-healthy-relationship-model/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/rest-columns-shadows-healthy-relationship-model/</guid><description>I co-created the Columns &amp;amp; Shadows model with friend / sex educator / curriculum writer extraordinaire Karen Rayne. We put our heads together to help sex educators answer a question a lot of students struggle with: what makes a relationship healthy or unhealthy?
Here's a quote from article I wrote to introduce the Columns &amp;amp; Shadows Model:
&amp;ldquo;It’s hard to define what a healthy relationship looks like because we all navigate relationships differently.</description></item><item><title>The Sexualitree</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/sexualitree/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/sexualitree/</guid><description>I co-created the Sexualitree model with friend / sex educator / curriculum writer extraordinaire Karen Rayne. We put our heads together to help sex educators introduce a popular concept to students: &amp;ldquo;comprehensive sexuality education.&amp;rdquo;
From the About page:
&amp;ldquo;The Sexualitree is a way to see how we experience sexuality in different ways. Sexuality affects us on different levels of our lives, and each person uniquely.&amp;rdquo;
We've created supplemental materials to help educators use the model, and it's been implemented in dozens of curricula.</description></item><item><title>The Safe Zone Project</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project/</guid><description>Meg and I created The Safe Zone Project in 2013 to serve as a free online resource for folks doing LGBTQ awareness and ally trainings (AKA &amp;ldquo;safe zone trainings&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>The Genderbread Person</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/genderbread-person/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/genderbread-person/</guid><description>I published my first version of the Genderbread Person, an adorable, digestible model for understanding the complexity of gender, to accompany an essay in 2011 (and made a more printer-friendly version early in 2012).
I went on to create several versions of this model, improving and tweaking it based on feedback, and it's been adapted and remixed by countless other educators and organizations over the years.
This was my spin on an idea that I was taught on back in college (in the early 2000s), which goes back in different forms for many decades.</description></item><item><title>It's Pronounced Metrosexual</title><link>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/its-pronounced-metrosexual/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.samuelkillermann.com/work/its-pronounced-metrosexual/</guid><description>I wrote the show that became &amp;ldquo;It's Pronounced Metrosexual&amp;rdquo; while I was in grad school.
It was my &amp;ldquo;Plan B&amp;rdquo; for if I don't find a job in higher education. We were still in a recession, and jobs were tough to come by.
The online resource aspect of IPM, by about 100-fold the most popular byproduct of the site, was the result of a suggestion by my partner at the time.</description></item></channel></rss>