<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Designer on Sam Killermann&#39;s Curriculum Vitae</title>
    <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/skills/designer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Designer on Sam Killermann&#39;s Curriculum Vitae</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://samuelkillermann.com/skills/designer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>This Site: Samuel Killermann Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/samuel-killermann-curriculum-vitae/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/samuel-killermann-curriculum-vitae/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the seventh version of samuelkillermann.com. At least &amp;ndash; I think that&amp;rsquo;s right. One thing I&amp;rsquo;m sure of: it&amp;rsquo;s been a linear path of &amp;ldquo;Each one is better than the last.&amp;rdquo;
Sometimes embarrassingly better. If you&amp;rsquo;re curious about what the old versions of this site looked like, by all means step into the Wayback Machine and take a tour. Don&amp;rsquo;t say I didn&amp;rsquo;t warn you.
So let&amp;rsquo;s talk about what I&amp;rsquo;ve got going on here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every Shirt is Political</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/every-shirt-is-political/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/every-shirt-is-political/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Every shirt is political. It’s not just about what a shirt says on the front; it’s about what you’re saying when you buy it or wear it.
If you buy a shirt that was manufactured with unethical labor, you’re making a statement in favor of abuse. The same goes for the corporation who you buy it from, or the materials it’s made with.&amp;rdquo; (from the About Page)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facilitating XYZ</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/facilitating-xyz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/facilitating-xyz/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;When many of us start facilitating, we find ourselves learning a new skill without a lot of guidance or direction. We are passionate about the information and content that we are communicating, but we’re often less versed in tips and techniques regarding how to communicate that information.
This project is a free online resource that is to ensure that none of us have to navigate this world of facilitation without guidance, direction, or support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sexualitree</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/sexualitree/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/sexualitree/</guid>
      <description>I co-created the Sexualitree model with friend / sex educator / curriculum writer extraordinaire Karen Rayne. We put our heads together to help sex educators introduce a popular concept to students: &amp;ldquo;comprehensive sexuality education.&amp;rdquo;
From the About page:
 &amp;ldquo;The Sexualitree is a way to see how we experience sexuality in different ways. Sexuality affects us on different levels of our lives, and each person uniquely.&amp;rdquo;
  We&amp;rsquo;ve created supplemental materials to help educators use the model, and it&amp;rsquo;s been implemented in dozens of curricula.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Magic of Facilitation</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/unlocking-the-magic-of-facilitation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/unlocking-the-magic-of-facilitation/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Have you ever been in a training and marveled at how quickly the time flew by?
Genuinely enjoyed a meeting you were expecting to dread? Learned something powerful about a topic you thought wouldn&amp;rsquo;t engage you? Experienced an intimate, vulnerable, transformative moment with a group of total strangers? Then you&amp;rsquo;ve witnessed the magic of facilitation.&amp;rdquo; (excerpt from the book description)
I wrote Unlocking the Magic of Facilitation with Meg Bolger, after spending a few years doing train-the-trainers with her through The Safe Zone Project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Socially Just Cards</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/socially-just-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/socially-just-cards/</guid>
      <description>An experiment in gift economy and social justice, SJC is where I serve as Head Elf.
The cards are all doodled and written by me, but that&amp;rsquo;s not the important part.
What&amp;rsquo;s exciting about this project was the bar I set for myself: can I create a business that sells a physical thing that is 100% socially/environmentally/globally just. That is, that doesn&amp;rsquo;t create harm or compromise in any way.
SJC is what was born.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Guide to Gender</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/guide-to-gender/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/guide-to-gender/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;A book about gender with no mention of the word &amp;lsquo;hegemony,&amp;rsquo; but plenty of references to Star Wars, The Matrix, Lord of the Rings, and Star Trek&amp;ndash; with less of a focus on overwhelming scholarship and more of a focus on enjoyable learning.&amp;rdquo; (excerpt from the book&amp;rsquo;s (first edition) description)
I wrote this book because a bunch of people asked me to. It was a synthesis of the ideas (1) I had been blogging about; (2) I&amp;rsquo;d been speaking about; and (3) that helped me better understand my gender, when I first set down the path of understanding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Safe Zone Project</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/safe-zone-project/</guid>
      <description>Meg and I created The Safe Zone Project in 2013 to serve as a free online resource for folks doing LGBTQ awareness and ally trainings (AKA &amp;ldquo;safe zone trainings&amp;rdquo;).
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Genderbread Person</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/genderbread-person/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/genderbread-person/</guid>
      <description>I published my first version of the Genderbread Person, an adorable, digestible model for understanding the complexity of gender, to accompany an essay in 2011 (and made a more printer-friendly version early in 2012).
 I went on to create several versions of this model, improving and tweaking it based on feedback, and it&amp;rsquo;s been adapted and remixed by countless other educators and organizations over the years.
This was my spin on an idea that I was taught on back in college (in the early 2000s), which goes back in different forms for many decades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Pronounced Metrosexual</title>
      <link>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/its-pronounced-metrosexual/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samuelkillermann.com/work/its-pronounced-metrosexual/</guid>
      <description>I wrote the show that became &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s Pronounced Metrosexual&amp;rdquo; while I was in grad school.
It was my &amp;ldquo;Plan B&amp;rdquo; for if I don&amp;rsquo;t find a job in higher education. We were still in a recession, and jobs were tough to come by.
The online resource aspect of IPM, by about 100-fold the most popular byproduct of the site, was the result of a suggestion by my partner at the time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>